[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "This is when I cry, Piers?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "It's just -- it's not what my life is about.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 23, "question": "You're not vain at all like that?", "qSentId": 22}, {"answer": "Literally a pair of socks.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 34, "question": "Literally a pair of socks?", "qSentId": 33}, {"answer": "Yes, I probably should write -- I called my publisher when all the debt business was going on.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 46, "question": "Wouldn't it be the chronic debt cure?", "qSentId": 45}, {"answer": "I think the number one safe haven where people put their money is to invest in yourself first.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 85, "question": "Where are the safe havens for people?", "qSentId": 84}, {"answer": "It means if you're -- if you use what I talk about, first diagnose the problem.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "What does that mean?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Is this when I cry, Piers?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 122, "question": "What is the way that people at the moment that haven't got much money, how can they find fulfillment without necessarily material things?", "qSentId": 121}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "-- who was -- you were part of a program to help him, right?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "Well, I think he's doing very well.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "How do you think he's doing in particular relation to the economy of this country?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "You don't want -- listen, you don't want to talk about what's going on out there at a birthday party.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "Better -- what better place to do this?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "ARPER: I completely agree with you.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "So what was he like?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "Yes, I -- you know, he plays hard and he wants to win.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "Is he aggressive when he gets wind up?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "You know, one thing that I've come to realize is that polls reflect present day fears, not future results.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "Do you worry for him?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I think that they have a pretty strong field.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 253, "question": "When you see the Republican candidates to date, what do you make of them?", "qSentId": 252}, {"answer": "Dangerous isn't the best word.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Who do you think is the most dangerous?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "You know, I don't know.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 258, "question": "Who's the one the next time you see the president you say, \"You just want to watch that one\"?", "qSentId": 257}, {"answer": "You know, I -- folks are able to have their own opinions, and I would never censor anyone and say they're wrong for their own opinion.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 269, "question": "Do you understand that, and what do you think of that?", "qSentId": 268}, {"answer": "I think you're painting an analogy that he's losing right now, and I --", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Does he have that thing in him to say, right -- like he might be doing now with America?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I don't -- I -- it's actually inaccurate, Piers.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Is that inaccurate?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "We are winning.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Is he winning, though, do you think?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 346, "question": "Was he a good come-from- behind kind of guy?", "qSentId": 345}, {"answer": "Absolutely, without question.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "So if you take any kind of assumption that he's not in a winning position right now, you'd back him to win?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "No, thank you.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 380, "question": "You won't hold it against me that you used to be on my college bedroom wall?", "qSentId": 379}, {"answer": "Well, it is a compliment.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "It's a compliment?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "But I've got such respect for you watching your career from extraordinary journalist, to \"The Apprentice.\"", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "A lot of sweat equity.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "How did that happen?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Oh, yes.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 408, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 407}, {"answer": "RELAND: I just knew it.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 410, "question": "What made you think that?", "qSentId": 409}, {"answer": "Oh, my goodness, yes.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "Have you had much failure?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, you're very kind.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Where is the failure?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Oh, my God.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "Because I haven't seen it?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "Literally a pair of stocks.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Literally a pair of socks?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "It's extremely different.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 493, "question": "That's a totally different thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 492}, {"answer": "Well, in the beginning, our socks were carried at a handful of sporting good stores, Big Five and a few others.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "What was the key -- when you began with the socks and stuff, what was the key moment for you that really propelled this from, you know, a small business into the big league?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Sure, yeah.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "Do you remember what it was?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "Thank you.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What's the answer?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 572}, {"answer": "Smashed up face, nose, smashed teeth, ripped shoulder, mouth, lips, eyes.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "What kind of injuries?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "The minute it happened I thought, OK, this is going to be an adventure.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "What did you learn about that?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "For me, it's everything.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 616, "question": "How important is it, do you think, to have -- if you are doing this kind of business, to have the backdrop of a good, stable family?", "qSentId": 615}, {"answer": "Some of them, like a few of them.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "But none of the models?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "There are so many.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 631, "question": "Who did you think was -- present company excepted, who did you think was the number one, the most beautiful model you have ever seen?", "qSentId": 630}, {"answer": "Oh, my goodness.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 633, "question": "ORGAN: If you could produce one magazine, say one \"Sports Illustrated\" before you died, and you could put one woman as the cover, it can't be you?", "qSentId": 632}, {"answer": "There were so many.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 635, "question": "Who would it be?", "qSentId": 634}, {"answer": "The pair of you.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 650, "question": "A what?", "qSentId": 649}, {"answer": "It still doesn't -- I still feel like she's here.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 677, "question": "What was that experience like for you?", "qSentId": 676}, {"answer": "Absolutely, in every way.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 682, "question": "A proper star, wasn't she?", "qSentId": 681}, {"answer": "People always said she was dying.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 691, "question": "As someone who knew her so well, what was something that really annoyed you the most about the way she was characterized?", "qSentId": 690}, {"answer": "Our business is about solutions.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "What's the thing you are pushing now?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "You know, it was interesting, because for years we were building our brand very quietly.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "Do you have a little laugh at them now?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "I'd say a slow learner, hopefully tough.", "docId": "110905pmt", "aSentId": 750, "question": "Do you like that?", "qSentId": 749}]